Now there is over 300 Hookah bars in the nation.
I am sure you can find one locally but what you should expect from going to a Hookah bar.
A lot of time are middle eastern owned.
A lot of them are coffee shops, don't have drinks they just have the Hookah.
You can drink tea and coffee but if you are going to go out to one of the night club versions such as are we, expect kind of a different experience.
It is not quite as laid back it is a little more of a night club experience.
Most of them are quite swanky so I would dress up and when you go to a Hookah bar it is not like going to the bar down the street.
It is not like that where you just go in and have a quick pint and leave.
The customers here they lounge out all night.
We, our normal customer average, I'd say they are here for at least three hours and many many times we have customers here that get here at 8 p.m. and they don't leave until 1.
So five hours is definitely not uncommon for people to relax and invite your friends to come in and they slowly come in and they join you and keep ordering Hookahs.
You can have many Hookahs on your table so that is a little bit of what you can expect going out to a Hookah bar.